Hmm… Princess.
王女殿下啊
She seems younger than me.
她好像比我小
After we get to know each other well, I hope she will call me "brother."
打好关系后 真希望她能叫我哥哥
Hey, Kazuma.
我说和真…
It is still not too late.
现在还不算太迟
Please turn down this matter.
拒绝这件事吧
Okay?
好吗
She is in charge of this nation.
对方可是这个国家的领导人物
Shut it up already!
烦死了
You had the gall to disagree with my proposal
我说要穿和服和裤裙接待
that I greet her in a kimono and hakama!
你居然反对我的意见
How am I supposed to meet her in those clothes,
我怎么可能
which I have never heard of?
穿那种听都没听过的衣服晋见她啊
Listen.
听好了
I will be dressing like this
在爱丽丝殿下来之前
until Princess Iris gets here,
我会暂时穿成这样
so you should also wear formal clothes.
所以你也要穿正式的服装
Enough talk.
吵死了
This is the moment for you to respond with "Yes, master".
这时候要说"遵命 主人"吧
Y-Yes, master.
遵…遵命 主人
I am a humble sow.
我是卑微的母猪
I did not ask you to say it over the top.
我没叫你说得这么夸张
(Konosuba S3)
《为美好的世界献上祝福！ 第三季》
(Episode 2: A Smile for the Unsmiling Girl)
(第2集 为不笑的少女献上微笑)
As expected,
果然
the usual clothes make me feel safer.
还是平常的打扮更让人安心
I allowed it because you begged me in tears.
是因为你哭着求我 我才允许的
After all, I am a noble.
我好歹也是个贵族
How could I dress like that?
怎么可能穿成那样…
You were clearly snickering behind my back.
明明背地里一直在窃笑
I was not.
我才没有
Get moving, you two.
你们两个 快走吧
Don't be so hasty.
别那么着急啦
There is a necessary task to be carried out before meeting Princess.
见王女之前还有一件重要的工作
The timing could not be better, the goods have arrived just now.
正好刚刚到货了哦
The product that you developed, Mr. Kazuma.
和真先生想出来的商品
Without my help, it couldn't have been done.
要不是有我帮忙 根本无法完成
Yeah, yeah.
是是
This is a useful tool in our country.
这是我们国家的便利工具
This is very convenient.
这个真的很方便呢
This is sure to be a hit with customers, Mr. Kazuma.
和真先生 这个一定能大卖
This Destroyer model is also one of my proudest works.
这款毁灭者造型也是我的得意作品
This eliminates the need for flint.
这样就不需要打火石了啊
I want one of these too.
我也想要一个这东西
You can have it.
请拿吧
I want one too, I want one too.
我也要 我也要一个
Pfft, pfft, pfft.
噗噗噗
It is only lighter,
只不过是个打火机
so why are you excited about it?
有什么好高兴的啊
I'll take one too.
我也拿一个
What are you doing?
你干嘛啊
I would also like to pick one.
也让我选一个啦
No, you have to pay.
不 你给我付钱
Why?
为什么啊
Why can Darkness and Megumin get it for free
为什么达克妮丝和惠惠可以拿
but not me?
只有我不行啊
Because you did nothing, right?
因为你什么也没做吧
Megumin helped with this.
惠惠有帮忙做这个
Darkness connected me to a major wholesaler's channel.
达克妮丝帮我介绍了 大型批发商的管道
You do nothing but eat and sleep at home.
而你只是待在家里 吃饱睡 睡饱吃
Just go out and get customers if you want it.
想让我分给你的话 就去外面招揽客人
Kazuma, you loser!
和真你这个没出息的人
You grabbed the clothes I took off to wash
你把我脱下来要洗的衣服
and sniffed desperately!
拿起来拼命闻
Initially, I was going to help you conceal it!
我本来想替你保密的
You ungrateful wretch.
你这个忘恩负义的家伙
Hey, don't talk nonsense!
喂 你不要乱讲啦
(Konosuba) Please do not look at me that way.
别这样 不要用那种眼神看我
So, next…
那么 接下来
Unbelievable as it may seem,
我拿出来的这块平淡无奇的手帕
doves came out of this plain handkerchief I pulled out.
真令人吃惊 竟然冒出鸽子
What is she doing?
她在做什么啊
That's putting the cart before the horse.
那样根本是本末倒置吧
Come on, perform some more.
再来 再多表演一下
Please, let me see something more thrilling.
拜托你 让我看更刺激的表演
Please don't tip.
请不要打赏
Because I'm not an artist.
因为我并不是艺人
Don't say that.
别这么说嘛
A tip of the hat to that wonderful trick.
为美好的表演献上打赏
You bastard.
你这混蛋
Are you not content to sprinkling holy water on our shop's doorknob every day,
日夜在我们店门的门把上 洒圣水还不满意
to the point where you start openly impeding our business operations?
甚至开始正大光明妨碍营业吗
Stay out of my way, you strange mask guy.
你不要妨碍我啦 带怪面具的家伙
This is a public roadway.
这里是公共道路
What is the problem with performing here?
我在这里表演有什么不对啊
Shut up!
吵死了
Today marks the debut of new merchandise that is critical to the store.
今天是攸关这家店未来的 新商品开卖日
-Could you please not get in the way of business? -Well… Listen.
-你能不能别妨碍营业 -那…那个 听我说
Guys.
各位
There is a new useful item in our shop today.
今天店里进了便利的新商品
Please come in and take a look.
请大家进来看看
(Konosuba) Wiz is looking like
我第一次看到
a shop manager for the first time.
维兹拿出店长该有的样子
Darkness, let go of me.
达克妮丝 放开我
Let me continue to perform.
让我继续表演啦
-Thank you. Thank you. -What is this?
-谢谢惠顾 谢谢惠顾 -这是什么 什么
-Two lighters and a Vanir mask, right? -What is it? Wow, awesome.
-两个打火机和巴尼尔面具对吧 -是什么啊 好厉害
Thank you.
谢谢惠顾
Thank you again.
我再次向你道谢
You restless lad, the vibe with your traveling companions
在旅行途中和伙伴气氛还不错
was great, but after that,
之后却完全没有进展
there was zero movement.
按捺不住的小鬼
D-Don't talk nonsense.
你…你不要胡说八道
I am certainly not restless.
我才没有按捺不住呢
Megumin, stop peeking at me all the time.
惠惠也不要一直偷看我啦
I certainly wasn't looking at you.
我才没有看你
Don't waver now.
你不要动摇啦
How can the words of a demon make you believe things that are not true?
怎么能被恶魔说的话耍得团团转
We should not talk about this.
不说这个了
Look at this grand scene.
看这个盛况
The 300 million Eris you deserve will be credited to your account.
你应得的三亿艾莉丝应该能进账
As an apology for keeping you waiting,
作为让你等待一阵子的赔礼
I will give you this.
这个送你吧
-What is this? -So cool, so amazing.
-这是什么 -好酷 好厉害…
-It's a mass-produced Vanir mask.
-是量产型巴尼尔面具
-Wearing it under the moonlight, the mysterious -So cool, so amazing.
-只要在月光下带着它 -好酷 好厉害…
-demonic power will enhance your magical power,
-神秘的恶魔力量就会使魔力上升
-improve blood circulation, smooth your skin, -So cool, so amazing.
-促进血液循环 皮肤也会变光滑 -好酷 好厉害…
-and put you in excellent condition.
-让人变得绝佳状态的东西
And this is one of the rarest, the black mask.
而且这是其中最稀有的黑面具
You can show it off to the kids.
你可以跟小朋友炫耀哦
-From that day forward, -I must perform this.
-从那天开始 -这个表演我一定要做
-Wiz's shop continues to thrive, -Let me do it. Let me perform till the end.
-维兹的店就一反常态 -让我表演…让我表演到最后
-going against the grain. -Calm down, Aqua.
-持续生意兴隆 -冷静点 阿库娅
And finally…
然后终于
Alright, you two.
好了 你们两个
You know what to do, right?
知道该做什么吧
Of course.
当然
I'll heat things up with my best party show.
我会用拿手的宴会表演炒热气氛
I won't let Darkness lose face.
不让达克妮丝丢脸的
I will also make a grand entrance
我也用华丽的登场
that will really surprise the princess.
让公主殿下大吃一惊吧
Kazuma.
和真
Where should I buy something that produces
能制造出烟雾弥漫效果的东西
a smoky effect and fireworks?
和烟火要去哪里买呢
-Are they really okay? -I'll lend you my treasured smoke bombs.
-她们真的没问题吗 -我借你珍藏的烟雾弹吧
Great.
太好了
-Hello, everyone. -Thank you.
-各位 -谢谢你
Today, I,
今天就由我
Lalatina Ford Dustiness,
达斯堤尼斯·福特·拉拉蒂娜
will be in charge of leading you.
负责带领你们
This is too loose.
这件太宽松了
I think a bit tighter would be better.
我觉得再窄一点比较好
T-There is no choice.
有…有什么办法
You can't hold up a knight's clothes without muscles.
骑士服没有肌肉根本撑不起来
Megumin, what's wrong with you?
惠惠 你怎么了
I have no idea
不知道为什么
why it fell off so suddenly.
一下子就掉下去了
Isn't there a smaller size?
没有更小件的吗
There is, but…
也不是没有
But that dress was worn by me when I was a child…
但那件洋装是我小时候穿的…
It hurts.
好痛
Don't pull my braids.
不要扯我的麻花辫
Megumin, what is this?
惠惠 这是什么啊
Is not this a monster-repelling smoke bomb and explosive potion?
这不是驱赶怪物的烟雾弹 和爆炸魔药吗
(Konosuba) Confiscated!
通通没收
Look, look.
你看你看
How is it?
怎么样
Oh.
哦
Stop staring at me.
不要一直盯着我看啦
Oh, oh.
哦哦
Alright.
好了
Listen up.
你们听着
Behave nicely.
千万不能做出失礼的行为哦
One wrong word
只要说错一句话
could give you the death penalty.
就有可能掉脑袋
What's the matter, Kazuma?
怎么了 和真
Let me tell you in advance.
先跟你们说一声
If the Princess wants me to go with her,
如果公主殿下要我到她身边
I might think about moving.
我有可能会考虑搬家
Please be mentally prepared for this.
这一点请你们做好心理准备
You view things too positively.
你的脑袋到底把事情想得多顺利啊
Listen.
听好了
I'll be responsible for chatting with Princess Iris.
我负责陪爱丽丝殿下聊天
All you have to do is eat and
你们只要一边吃饭
nod your head yes.
一边点头附和就好
So…
那么
Let's go in.
进去吧
Princess Iris, sorry for keeping you waiting.
爱丽丝殿下 让您久等了
They are both my friends
他们是我的朋友
and my adventuring companions.
同时也是冒险伙伴
Satou Kazuma and his peers.
佐藤和真和他的同行者
Truly unexpected.
真令人意外
This world has not disappointed my expectations.
这个世界没有辜负我的期待
It's indeed rare.
还真是少见
This is the first princess of this country,
这位是这个国家的第一王女
Princess Iris Stylish-Sword Belzerg.
贝尔泽格·史岱历什·索德·爱丽丝殿下
You three,
你们三个
greet the Princess.
礼貌地打声招呼吧
I am Aqua, serving as the Archpriest.
我是担任大祭司的阿库娅
It is a pleasure to meet you.
请您多多指教
So
那么
as a greeting, let me perform one of my talents.
当作问候 我来表演一项才艺吧
Please excuse me, I have something to say to her.
失礼了 我有话要跟伙伴说
Hey, let go of me!
喂 放开我
I'm about to perform my best talent right now.
我现在要表演拿手的才艺
A pleasure to meet you, Princess.
幸会 王女殿下
My name is Megu--
我的名字叫惠…
Hey, didn't I say to behave properly?
喂 我不是说要好好表现吗
Hey!
喂
That being said,
话说回来
Princess is really adorable!
王女殿下真的好可爱啊
Is she very shy?
她是不是很怕生呢
Despicable fellow.
卑贱的家伙
You must not stare at the royalty with such impolite eyes.
不能用那种没礼貌的眼神盯着王族
Bow low, avoid making eye contact,
把头低下来 不准视线相交
and then introduce yourself and share your adventure tale.
然后赶快打招呼并说出冒险故事
That's what Her Highness said.
殿下这么说
I see.
原来如此
Change!
换人
(Konosuba) Princess Iris!
爱丽丝殿下
My companions are too nervous.
我的伙伴们太紧张了
So they are a bit overexcited.
所以有点亢奋
Please give me a moment.
请给我一点时间
You jerk…
你这家伙真是…
What does "change" mean?
换人是什么意思
This isn't what we agreed on, right?
这跟我们说好的不一样吧
That's my line.
这是我要说的台词
I can't believe I've had expectations from Her Highness.
居然让我对公主殿下有所期待
What's with that?
那是怎样啊
I was hoping she would say something like,
我本来还期待她说
"I long for the world beyond,
"我很向往外面的世界"
O brave adventurer,
"勇敢的冒险者大人"
let me hear your tales
"让我听听你的冒险故事吧"
of adventure."
这样的话耶
With her attitude like that, how are we going to eat together?
那样子还聚什么餐啊
Is she looking down on me?
瞧不起人吗
It's done.
完成了
As a symbol of friendship,
作为友好的象征
please accept this.
请先收下这个吧
It is a masterpiece that highlights every detail,
这是连翘起来 没有梳好的头发
including unkempt hair.
都完美呈现出来的杰作
Princess Iris,
爱丽丝殿下
I will have these rude people kicked out right away.
我现在就把这些无礼之徒赶出去
I-I'm sorry.
对…对不起
It is incredible that such an outstanding sand painting
居然在这么短的时间
could be created in such a short period of time.
画出如此出色的沙画
And you even got Lalatina,
而且
who is usually quiet and calm,
还让沉默寡言又冷静的拉拉蒂娜
to show a rare sign of stress.
露出少见的慌张神情
So it's alright.
所以没关系
That's what Her Highness said.
殿下这么说
Then let us begin the meal.
那我们开始用餐吧
You must be the Cursed Sword Hero that Mitsurugi mentioned, right?
你就是魔剑勇者御剑说的人吧
Tell me your story.
让我听听你的故事吧
That's what Her Highness said.
殿下这么说
I would love to hear it too.
我也很想听
The story of how you impressed Mr. Mitsurugi.
你让御剑先生刮目相看的故事
Alright.
好吧
In a later stage, I adjusted to the circumstances and laid a trap,
后来我就临机应变 设下陷阱
using myself as bait
故意让自己当诱饵
to expose Sylvia's vulnerability.
制造席薇亚的弱点
Your style of fighting
我还是第一次听到
is unlike anything I have ever heard of.
有人像你这样战斗
So far,
到目前为止
all the stories I have heard about heroes
我听到的都是绝对不会输的勇者
have involved them vanquishing monsters by themselves.
单方面除掉怪物的故事
That's what Her Highness said.
殿下这么说
My constant pursuit of personal growth
王女殿下 这一点
in the face of formidable challenges
就是我这种常常和强悍的对手较量
is one way that I differ from them,
每天都追求进步的人
Princess.
与他们的不同之处吧
A shut-in is talking nonsense.
不想出门的人在胡说八道
Awesome.
太优秀了
Just before you became an adventurer, what did you do for a living?
成为冒险者前你从事什么工作
That's what Her Highness asked.
殿下这么问
I am also interested.
我也很好奇
Please tell us.
请告诉我们
Before I came to this country,
来到这个国家之前
it was my job to watch over my family as they came home.
我的工作是守护家人的归宿
Every day, I worked on my skills in silence,
每天默默磨练自己的技能
keeping important places
保护重要的场所
safe from disaster.
不让它被灾厄袭击
However, nobody understood or complimented me.
尽管如此 却得不到任何人的理解和赞美
That is a tragic job.
是很可悲的工作
Is it similar to the role of a castle guard?
是类似城堡守卫的工作吗
It seems that you, too, played a silent role
你也默默地
in protecting your hometown from various disasters.
保护故乡不被各种灾厄袭击吧
On occasion, I have to figure out how to deal with individuals
想办法应付说只要三个月就好
who try to force me into contracts by claiming that three months is sufficient.
逼我缔结契约的人
In short, a lot has happened.
总之发生过很多事
Contracts?
契约…
Did you repel the demon on your own?
你一个人击退了恶魔吗
Home security…
自家保全…
(Konosuba) I wasn't lying!
我可没有说谎
Just so you can beat Mr. Mitsurugi…
居然能赢过御剑先生
Would you mind showing me
当作将来的参考
your adventurer card so I can use it as a reference?
我能看看和真先生的冒险者卡片吗
How could I possibly let her see
我那张充满个性的冒险者卡片
my personalized adventurer card?
怎么能给她看啊
I would be exposed in an instant
你是在哪里学到巫妖技能的?
if she asked me, "Where did you learn Lich?"
如果被这么问就马上穿帮了
Asking an adventurer to reveal his card seems inappropriate.
要冒险者亮出底牌似乎不太好
Rather than that…
比起这个
Aqua,
阿库娅
it is time for you to show off your big talent.
差不多该表演你拿手的才艺了
I drew a lovely sand painting.
我今天已经画了好看的沙画
I am done for the day.
就不表演了
Hey!
喂
Bring over some more bubble wine.
再多拿一些这个泡泡酒过来
-Bring it here quickly. -I won't tell anyone.
-快拿过来 -我不会告诉别人
Or
还是说
is it do you have a reason not to let other people see it?
你有不能给人看的理由吗
There is indeed a reason not to show it to others.
就是有不能给人看的理由
The job this person has is the weakest,
这个人从事最弱职业
and he might be too embarrassed to tell you this.
他可能是不好意思 让你们知道这件事
T-That's how it is.
就…就是这样
What you just said raises suspicions.
你刚刚说的话也很可疑
Did you really defeat Mr. Mitsurugi?
你真的打赢过御剑先生吗
I can't tell her that
我…我不能告诉她
I won by using Steal
我是出其不意用Steal
to steal his Cursed Sword.
抢走他的魔剑才打赢的
Um…
那…那个
I find it hard to believe that someone
剑术大师御剑先生
from the lowest profession could
会输给最弱职业的人
defeat Mr. Mitsurugi, the Swordsmanship Master.
真是难以置信
Are you deceiving me?
你是不是对我说谎了
And he is very handsome.
而且他长得很帅
That's what Her Highness said.
殿下这么说
I think so too.
我也这么想
He is very handsome.
他长得很帅
Hey, you guys!
喂 你们这些家伙
I'd beat you up!
就算是我也会揍人哦
Insolent man!
无礼之徒
How dare you address the royal family as "you guys"?
怎么能对王族说"你们这些家伙"
Saying things that invite mockery,
说出那种像是要别人吐槽的话
then becoming enraged when someone mocks.
结果别人一吐槽就发火
I am very sorry.
十分抱歉
After all, he lacks manners.
毕竟他是连礼仪都不懂的人
For my sake,
请看在我的面子上
please forgive him for being rude.
原谅他的失礼吧
Considering Dustiness's significant impact
看在对这个国家有着伟大功绩的
on our nation,
达斯堤尼斯的面子上
I will refrain from pursuing it.
我就不追究了
But I feel very disappointed.
但我觉得很扫兴
I will reward you for telling me an adventure story.
我会给你讲述冒险故事的奖励
Please accept your reward and depart immediately,
那个最弱职业的骗子
you con artist from the lowest profession.
立刻带着它离开吧
That's what Her Highness said.
殿下这么说
My goodness, that is excessive.
哎呀 说得真过分呢
But thanks to Darkness,
不过托达克妮丝的福
I was saved.
我得救了
Hurry back.
快点回去吧
That hurts.
好痛
Hey, Megumin, what are you doing?
喂 惠惠 你在做什么
Stop it.
快住手
Hey.
喂
Not good.
不妙
Megumin prioritizes companions the most.
惠惠是最重视伙伴的人
If someone picks a fight, she will surely retaliate.
有人找碴 她一定会反击
Strange.
奇怪
I was worried that you would definitely be mad.
我还担心你一定会抓狂呢
If it were just me,
如果只有我一个人
I would not endure it.
我当然不会忍
It would be hard for you, Darkness,
要是我在这里抓狂
if I got mad here, right?
达克妮丝会伤脑筋吧
Princess Iris.
爱丽丝殿下
Could you take back
您能不能收回
what you said about him being a con artist?
刚刚说他是骗子这句话呢
This man has not lied,
这个男人虽然讲话很浮夸
despite his exaggerated claims.
但他并没有说谎
Furthermore, in times of crisis,
而且尽管他是最弱职业
he is more dependable than anybody else,
但是在紧要关头
even though his profession is the weakest.
却比任何人都要可靠
Princess Iris, I implore you
我拜托您 爱丽丝殿下
to retract your previous statement
能不能请您订正刚刚说的话
and offer an apology to him.
并向他道歉呢
Lord Dustiness!
达斯堤尼斯卿
I won't apologize!
我不道歉
Since you said he was not lying,
既然你说他没说谎
ask him to describe
就叫那个男人说明
how he beat Mr. Mitsurugi.
他是怎么打赢御剑先生的
If he can't do that,
如果他做不到
he is weak
就代表他很弱
and just a blowhard con artist--
只是会耍嘴皮子的骗…
What are you doing, Lord Dustiness?
你在做什么 达斯堤尼斯卿
No!
不行
Princess Iris.
爱丽丝殿下
I'm sorry.
失礼了
However, you should not speak ill of someone
但是您不能这样说拼命战斗
who fought bravely and achieved so much.
留下如此辉煌功绩的人
He is under no obligation
他也没有责任
to explain to you how he defeated the Cursed Sword Guy.
向您说明自己是怎么 打赢魔剑剑士的
And even if he lost,
而且 就算没打赢
you still have no right to scold him severely.
他也没有理由被您痛骂
Alright, I understand.
好吧 我知道了
My companion is obviously trying to protect me,
既然伙伴这么护着我
so I can't remain silent.
我当然不能不说了
Despite its lack of grace,
虽然不怎么帅气
I will show you
我就让你们看看
how I defeated Mitsurugi.
我是怎么打赢御剑的
Enough.
够了
Claire, I'm alright now.
克莱儿 我已经不要紧了
Why has her attitude taken such a complete and utter turn?
她的态度为什么一百八十度大转变
Maybe her actual character is not so terrible.
难道她的本性并不坏吗
Given your willingness, I will not intervene.
既然你说好 我就不会阻止你
Go ahead, Kazuma.
做吧 和真
You shouldn't lose to her, right?
你应该不会输给她吧
Of course not.
那当然啦
Think about the opponents I've faced before.
想想我之前交手过的对象吧
Cursed Sword Guy and the leaders of the Devil King's Army.
魔剑剑士和魔王军干部
And those hefty reward targets.
还有重量级的悬赏目标
I usually fight such opponents.
我平时都跟这样的对手较量
I am going to steal that dangerous sword.
我就先抢走那把危险的剑
Eat this!
接我这招吧
Steal!
Steal
Alright. Now I'm going to--
很好 就这样一鼓作气…
Sorry, this…
抱歉 这个…
Please take this back.
还给你
-You jerk! -I'm sorry!
-你这家伙真是… -对不起
Why can't you do it right?
为什么没办法帅气地做好啊
I'm sorry.
对不起
Um…
那个…
I'm very sorry.
非常抱歉
Please don't mind it.
请别在意
After all, the wound has healed.
反正伤口已经复原了
It's best to pretend it never happened.
当作没发生过是最好的
Nonetheless,
不过
I was genuinely surprised that she managed to heal that wound flawlessly.
真没想到她能完美治好那个伤口
And, Lord Dustiness, your unwavering attitude.
还有达斯堤尼斯卿 那种坚忍的态度
Plus, this individual is none other than the famous Crimson Demon.
这位还是大名鼎鼎的红魔族
If it were you,
如果是你们
it would make sense to be able to repel the leaders of the Devil King's Army.
能击退魔王的干部也很合理
As for Mr. Kazuma…
至于和真先生…
What makes you look at me with doubt?
为什么只对我投以怀疑的目光啊
It would be better if you told him that yourself.
这个您还是自己告诉他比较好哦
Don't worry.
别担心
Mr. Kazuma appears helpless
和真先生看起来
against someone like Princess Iris, you see.
对爱丽丝殿下这样的人 没有抵抗力哦
It seems they are talking about something rude.
她们好像在说什么失礼的话
Apologies for earlier labeling you as a con artist.
对不起 说你是骗子
Can you tell me
你还能…
some more adventure stories?
再跟我讲冒险故事吗
Sure.
我很乐意
Then it is time to return to the castle.
那我们回城堡了
Princess Iris.
爱丽丝殿下
Let us talk more when we visit
等我们去王都的时候
the royal capital.
再跟您聊吧
Farewell.
再会
Then, Princess,
那么 王女殿下
see you next time.
我们下次再见
Tele…
Tele…
-What are you saying? -port
-你在说什么啊 -port
What?
什么
P-Princess Iris?
爱…爱丽丝殿下?
Um…What's going on?
呃 这是…
Did not you say
你不是说过
you would tell me more adventure stories?
会继续跟我讲冒险故事吗
Worthy of being the leader of the nobles.
不愧是贵族的首领
That's a hell of a way to behave.
旁若无人的行为有够夸张
(Episode 3: Re-Educate this Arrogant Girl)
(第3集 为自大的少女 进行再次教育)
Long time no see, Devil King.
好久不见 魔王大人
I am the Deadly Poison Slime, Hans.
我是剧毒史莱姆汉斯
I started selling something called
我最近开始在三途川
"Slime Red Bean Soup" at Sanzu River not long ago…
卖一种叫"史莱姆 红豆汤"的东西…